VERONIKA HARBACHOVA

Austin, TX | veronika.har@hotmail.com

Profile Summary

Linguist turned web developer blends soft skills of adaptability and openmindedness with hard skills of web design. Cross-functional collaboration with tech teams and successful experience of working as a part of one. Experience in logistics honed my problem-solving, analytical and leadership skills.

Education

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development

CareerFoundry | 01/2019 - 11/2019

- 300+ hours of training/mentoring with industry leading Front-End and Senior Full-Stack Web Developer.
- Intensive project-based training program with a focus on JavaScript, HTML, CSS and most prominent libraries, frameworks and tools;
- To see my skills in action, visit https://veronikaharbachova.netlify.com/

MA in Linguistics

Dalian University of Technology | 09/2008 - 07/2011

BA in Linguistics

Belarusian State University | 09/2003 - 06/2008

Employment History

Wallenborn Transports S.A – Luxembourg, Luxembourg

Supply Chain Specialist | 02/2015 – 07/2016

- ✓ Provided customer support and account management for Qatar Airlines EU freight handling. Established strong relationship with QA office in Atlanta.
- ✓ Analyzed the company's internal S&OP software (AS-TRANS) and cooperated with an outsourced development team on its improvement;

Lear Corporation – Shanghai, China

Supply Chain Specialist | 11/2013 – 06/2014

- ✓ Lead Logistics Network Optimization for China Seating: identified potential of 20-25% (\$300k annually) savings;
- ✓ Supported LEAR Malaysia Supply Chain recovery;

Generation_P – *Minsk*, *Belarus*

XSLT developer / Assistant Team-Leader | 09/2007 - 08/2008

- ✓ Achieved full technical competency in 3 months without any prior experience (CVS repo; PAROS (POST/GET); Oxygen+Eclipse; XML etc);
- ✓ Assistant Team-Leader supervised team performing patch-and-release responsibilities and negotiated business solutions with foreign customers.

Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React.js

Node.js

jQuery

Redux

React Native

PWA

APIs

Photoshop

Bootstrap

Responsive Design

TDD

Toolkit

NPM

TypeScript

Sass

Jest/Enzyme

CodePen

GitHub

Chrome Developer Tools